# Chapman Cheng's Resume

Lives in Tseung Kwan O, Hong Kong

Contact: (+852) 9267 4177 / chapman.reg@gmail.com

Chapman is an aspiring front-end web developer and he aim to become full-stack web developer. He is looking for jobs that could improve his coding skills.

He has 5 years of experiences of community work which is related to government policies and law. He often finds ways to improve the efficient and effectiveness of his works. Chapman believes learning new skill is a lifelong objective.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# District Council Office of Hon James TO Kun-sun

Head of office and community officer

September 2015 - April 2018

## Legislative Council Office of Hon James TO Kun-sun

— Community officer

May 2013 - August 2015

- Assist Legco member office for both Legislative Council and District Council office
- answering public enquiries
- research in government policies
- creating promotional materials
- arranging outdoor events.
- organized election campaign during 2015 and 2016 Legco and DC

#### **SKILLS**

**Programming Languages** 

- HTML5
- CSS3
- SASS (SCSS)
- jQuery
- JavaScript (ES6)
- Git
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator

Operating System:

Windows

#### **LANGUAGES**

Cantonese, English, Mandarin

**Darton Limited**— *Clerk* May 2011 - December 2012

### **QUALIFICATION & ACHIEVEMENTS**

Front End Web Development Techdegree (Treehouse E-learning) - (2019)

**IELTS** - overall band score 6.5 (2009)

#### **EDUCATION**

**De Montfort University**, Hong Kong—Bachelor of Arts in Public Administrative and Management (Second Class Upper Division Honours)

February 2015 - July 2016

Equipped knowledge and skills of public administration, public sector management, public policy making. Aims to combine the study of applied politics with the management of modern society.

The Chinese University of Hong Kong - Tung Wah Group of Hospitals Community **College**, Hong Kong — Associate Degree of Science in Three-dimensional and Product Design (with merit)

September 2006- September 2009

Learned the process of industrial designing and prototyping a physical tangible product, along with CAD drawing, and started to learn to problem solving. Cumulative GPA score of 3.1.

in Profile: www.linkedin.com/in/chapmancheng